Lesson 11. Bob drives a hard bargain.
Carol from the village market calls Bob to discuss Susan's scrumptious cookies.
Carolyn Bob discuss how much Bob will receive for each cookie.
Hi Bob, how's it going?
Fine, thanks Carol. How are you?
Can't complain. Bob, I've had a chance to crunch some numbers.
I can pay you 50 cents per cookie.
That's out of the question. At that price, it's not worth our while.
The ingredients alone cost us 30 cents per cookie.
Okay, let me sweeten the deal. 60 cents per cookie?
Carol, my wife and I need to make a living from this business.
Okay, okay. You've twisted my arm.
I'll pay you 75 cents per cookie. Take it or leave it.
Now you're talking. We'll take it.
You drive a hard bargain, Bob.
Yes, but we make a good cookie.
Let's get the ball rolling.
Bring me 2,000 cookies on Monday morning by 9 a.m.